hello I hope you are doing an amazing
job
today having an incredible day anyways
listen I
am
here what is that that is a that is a
leave got to take the leaves off that we
we we we pay these guys to come out here
and do this but you know they're good my
my guy uh Mason is awesome I'm I'm to
send in this video he'll laugh cuz he'll
be like I did my job that fell
after Mason I know you uh anyways
so I have to be somewhere in
about 20
minutes um but I wanted to come to you
real
quick and make a video some of you'all
have been wondering like why I keep
making these videos in the swimming pool
things like this what the purpose is if
it's like some ruse or some kind of a
like marketing thing they're like I
don't have a swimming pool so I can't be
successful in online marketing like
Jeremiah and so like here's the thing
okay I go in my swimming
pool
when my wife
and son are taking care
of and we have uh my sister-in-law here
that helps us out at the
house and that's it's where it's where I
get to
relax and
chill
and I get to show
up in the best
most confident version of
myself when I'm here let me go to the
other side here cuz I know this is a
little loud over here
this Fountain we need to get it scrubbed
down too we got like a whole list of
stuff that the pool company's like hey
we need to do and help you with all
right anyway some of yall are like
what's the point of this
video everything
so let me prop it up here so for me
to be able
to show up as like the best most
powerful version of myself in business
and when I make videos and marketing
videos and things like that I have
to what do you call it I have to be in a
very good head
space it's not that I'm in a bad head
space all the time it's just that um I'm
focused on being a
dad the the logistics of building and
growing a
business
and when it comes
to when it comes to let me move this
just a little bit there there we go when
it comes to making content on social
media if you can show up especially if
you're trying to grow a business if you
can show up as the most confident vers
of
yourself
where
you show
up fully believing in what you were
called to do nobody can question it you
have a little bit of a like a not take
Guff from anybody type attitude and so
for me what I find is that when I'm in
my pool
here when I'm in my swimming pool and I
have
you know uh a drink that I like right
here I used to DJ I used to go to like
pool parties and stuff all the time and
it was one of my happiest places where I
got to like really show up
confidently and so for me I find that
like when I'm in the swimming pool
myself and I am you know maybe I got
like a like a like a drink that I'm
drinking or something like
that that that's the like that's how I I
process information
better and I show
up not at all being concerned with what
anybody thinks about me at all and so
like this video again I get it maybe
you're watching this right now you're
like what's the point get to the point
the video is the point this video right
right
here is a
lesson by itself and that's what I want
you to pay attention to is I want you to
pay attention to the fact
that the fact that this video exists is
the
lesson I'm going to swim over here real
quick had to dunk the camera just a
little bit can you still hear
me
here if we pull the water out you should
be able to hear it just fine okay so let
me go to the deep end here let me swim a
little bit for me I show up and I'm able
to be very confident especially when I'm
about to go do something really hard
really scary something that I've not
done in a while that's something that I
have to do in the next 15 minutes I have
to go do it's kind of scary it's
something that I've not done in a while
it's kind
of
stressful and so I'm here in my swimming
pool but I also need to make
content to promote my business to
promote the event that I'm hosting
tomorrow I'm hosting a live
event on Zoom let me go to the edge
here I'm hosting a live event on Zoom
tomorrow where I'm going to teach you
how to create your own digital
course how we do it what my method is
for this what the best practices
are that I believe that you need to do
this is not standing up on its own right
here very
well there we
go but for me to make the best content I
have
to be in the right head spot face and
when you're raising kids I have one kid
so I don't even know I can't imagine
when you got
multiple when you're raising
kids it's hard to find the best space in
your life to be able to create
content and to feel confident and to
show up as the best version of yourself
for the best lessons now here's the cool
part about it this video I get it seven
minutes long eight minutes I still
haven't
giving you very much good content yet G
right like I'm sure I got people I get
people all the time they're just they're
angry that my videos have no focus and
anyways you can clip it like this one I
can clip it I can literally I have a
video editor who's amazing who works for
me who watches videos like this and
clips them and so like I'm going to I'm
going to tell her like start at 8
minutes and go find something because
that's where I'm actually going to
probably have the meat and potatoes of
this this video I'll probably put in the
description skip to 8 minutes if you
want to actually see me get to the point
right you know but as far as that goes
um
I find that if I can create environments
and for me the swimming pool is that the
swimming pool is one of those
environments where I can create an
environment where I get to show up as
the best version of myself the most
confident version of myself and and
that's what helps me create the best
content and I do it throughout my day
and things like that so like I found a
pocket of time right now I have
something I got to go do in 11 minutes
that is very stress
inducing
anxiety uh creating and instead I am
intentionally
doing what most would say is a terrible
idea
making content on social media in a
swimming
pool but for me it's
actually the best thing to do because
what I'm doing is I'm calming my brain
I'm calming my mind I'm calming my
spirit I'm I'm bringing myself into
alignment to show up as the best version
of myself right now and I put myself
into an environment where I can do that
my swimming pool is that it's a heated
swimming pool right now it's it's heated
it's it was it's heated up to
95° and it's it's been below 40 all week
here in Texas in a in in
Austin and so all that to say some of
y'all put way too much energy and
thought into making the perfect piece of
content when all you got to learn how to
do is is cultivate an atmosphere inside
of yourself and a mental framework of
stability and and it doesn't have to be
that way all the time right it does
doesn't have to be that way in every
moment of your
life
but I mean that's what we strive to
right we'd like it to be that way I
I I as a as a husband as a leader as a
as a
father being calm Under
Pressure that's wisdom and we live in a
world today where
you it's not just enough to show
up calm Under
Pressure you have to have kindness and
compassion and a heart and actually care
about people and so how do we bring all
those pieces together for me it's here I
I made a joke I was like this is my
Roman Empire you know this is where this
is like I and I treated like my bath my
uh my pool like it's like a Roman bath
house where I've created an cultivated I
do AI research in here I
do
um content creation I create some of my
Facebook ads things like that uh another
area that I do this is I'll when I go
for walks I walk around my
neighborhood
um in my car but obviously when I'm
driving I have an app that I can even
record myself when I'm driving audio and
it transcribes it to create blog posts
and things like that and so like I've
created in my life
scenarios where I can create really good
quality content to put out there and to
impact my audience and things like that
without having
to spend hours and hours and hours or
even going into rituals to do this these
aren't rituals for me what this is is is
I put myself into environments where the
ritual happens so like for instance let
me let me bring it back over here real
quick
for
instance when I was talking about like
having a drink by the pool and things
like that it's a it's a it's a
ritual that just by getting in here gets
me into the State of Mind of
creativity is what it is and you can
cultivate these rituals in any part of
your life you don't need a swimming pool
you don't need to drink a fizzy drink or
something like by the way this is not
alcoholic either uh this is some paleo
Mexican powder with element uh
electrolytes and lime juice combined
with sparkling water but it tastes like
a margarita it tells my brain that I'm
in
the um pool party State of Mind is what
it is when I go into that state of mind
it's the way that I'm able to tap into
showing up as the most excited happy
joyful version of myself to create the
best kind of content
and so that's why you've been
finding like I've been doing this in my
swimming pool a lot but now I have a
framework of
it that I'm going to start teaching you
on my social media about how you can
create content you don't need a swimming
pool you don't need a you don't need a
you don't need an isolated white room or
a prison cell to be able to create the
best content no you can make it in the
chaos of your home you can make it in
the in the in the middle of your day
anywhere you just take five minutes you
can tap into it and you create a way
to focus
yourself to show up as the best version
of yourself and what you do is you
create a trigger so create you create
like a positive trigger so for me
getting into the pool having that that
drink it's one of the positive triggers
that snaps me instantly into the most
creative version of myself possible to
create content marketing ideas things
like that and I don't have to have
alcohol to do it I used to drink alcohol
to say oh this is where my creativity
shows up and now I
don't you know I play video games
sometimes for like 30 minutes and it
steps me into that I play video games
because it it it puts my brain and I
play different types of games too like
I'll play a strategy game if I'm trying
to strategize things I'll play like a
shooter game if I need to get on a a
fast paced sales call or a webinar
things like that and so it gets my mind
State
into being able to show
up as the best version of myself and so
again the swimming pool is just
a uh it's really a prop at this point
for you of the of the message that I'm
trying to get across is that you can
make content content happens and we need
to stop focusing so much on the
engagement or the
numbers and show and focus and not even
what you're going to say but focus more
on cultivating inside of you an internal
mental and multi sensory atmosphere of
being able to show up as the best
version of yourself you ever notice like
when you clean up clutter in your house
you're more focused it's one of those
things it's a ritual that gets you into
that I find I'm very focused with my
to-do schedule when I do the dishes and
so I've created these different moments
and rituals and things like this to get
me to show up as the best version of
myself my wife does this too you know
when she wakes
up have breakfast go have a shower
things like this and and so like all
human beings we do this and if you've
ever noticed and you're going to start
noticing it now that when you show up as
the worst version of
yourself I would bet you that there's a
chain of events that gets you there as
well
cuz I know it was for
me I struggled for years with alcohol I
struggled for a long time
with
um just not being the the version of
myself that I was born to be
and I'm not perfect by any means I'm not
claiming to be some of y'all might hear
this as like oh he's claiming he's got
all the answers I don't I don't at all I
don't even have some of
them but I can tell you what's worked
for me I know a lot of people come to me
and look at you know how can I create
content that attracts people to
my webinars or trainings or Builds an
audience on social media how do you
build a social media following people
say all the time by doing this by doing
exactly what I'm doing right now you
cultivate inside of yourself an
atmosphere and an internal energy that
helps you show up as the best version of
yourself at all
times and then you press
record on this little device and you
capture
it you can use AI to transcribe it you
can use the AI to answer questions and
help you brainstorm new ideas for new
ways to express yourself turn it into
marketing materials turn it
into language and ways to do that and
and and and then what you could do is
you could take all of this and once you
start doing this in your normal everyday
life or you're just making content or
you're just you're just sharing Thoughts
with people on social
media you get an idea for a course you
can create an online course and you
start teaching People based on things
that you already have experienced in you
can sell that for
$1,000 to a thousand
people and now you've made a million
bucks and that's exactly what I show
people how to do and that's exactly what
I'm going to be showing you how to do on
Saturday as well so if you want to know
how to create an online course from
scratch quickly easily without
struggling without wondering can I make
this work this Saturday tomorrow morning
we're going to meet up and I'm going to
walk you through that all right I'll see
you there talk soon